The first part of my presentation
will be the presentation part of the system.
The second part is the Q&A part.
If the presentation part of my system,
if you want to take a break,
I will take a break when I finish the presentation
in the system part.
I will finish the presentation
and I will go to the Q&A part.
As you already know,
I am instructing you to access to the link
w The first way is to go to w The second way
is to access w However, this side will be less efficient.
This is the system of the party's implementation of activities. . .
There is a login page like this
and there is an application download link
of the app versions,
including both mobile phones
and iPads and tablets for each iOS and Android version
of the application.
When you log in to the login page,
you install the app to the correct purpose of the app version,
that is,
to use it at all times, everywhere.
When we go to school, when we go home,
when we go to work, etc.
And on the support screen,
there is a hotline line,
like the hotline line
for customer care of netizens.
When I call, there will be
a hotline team of us,
always recording the system.
However, when the whole country calls,
sometimes the hotline will be busy.
Like those netizens who call
the hotline of netizens,
there are more likes,
but it is still lagging.
Next, you have the mobile number hotline.
This mobile number may sometimes be me holding the phone,
sometimes it may be a few other people holding the phone,
we will divide it into subordinates.
However, you guys just call
this phone number except when the machine is busy,
but where it will usually listen
and the person holding the hotline
will answer it more deeply.
Third, the question that is often asked Then
you click on it,
it will have a common question
file like this.
Then you can find the questions
that you are interested in.
In this part, there are also more than 100 questions
that the whole country is most familiar with, most used.
Then you can also take the initiative.
to help with the questions
we often get. Besides,
you will be able to log in with the citizen's residence here.
is the account that you have received and the default password.
is 6 number 2, a small a big plus.
You can change the password after you have received
and entered the code.
And when you forget the password,
you can click "Forget password"
and enter your account name
and enter the code.
The code will return the OTP code
to your phone.
In addition, you can click ... by VNAD account,
you will log in VNAD on your phone
and you will enter or you log in by by VNID's username and password.
After that, you will also be directed
to the employment management software.
Those are the ways to log in.
There are two ways to log in.
After the instructions,
you will log in to the system.
I will log in to the system.
I am installing a TET account of Cam Ranh Party.
According to what you are entering,
I will enter OTV. With the first entry,
you will enter the OTP
and this OTP will be saved on a 30day period.
Please note that it is 30 days.
And on a period, for example,
if you are entering on Chrome,
then the username tab
will be saved on 30 days.
If you enter Firefox,
it will also be saved for 30 days.
After entering, you will have a main page like this.
And at the right corner of the screen,
in the Help section, Yeah.
If I talk too fast, please slow down.
In the Help Store,
there is a guide to use all modules.
For all modules, such as how to log in,
There will be instructions for each role in this zip.
There will be a leader
and a postman in each role.
Also a postman and a postman on mobile.
This is a postman and a postman on the web.
Then the documents will be somewhere,
some of them will be long read,
then you will listen to the interview,
then one Today is the second session,
so it will be easier for you to read the documents.
And on the team,
I will also send you videos of each step
for you to practice.
When there is a real document,
you practice every day,
then every day when you come to the agency,
you have to open the system
and do it as a habit,
then you will get used to it gradually.
In this page, you can drag and drop the cards like this.
On the left side,
you can see the menu bar.
That's the main page and the login page.
Today, there will also be managers in the district.
I will introduce each role.
For example, I will go to the basic role of the manager.
After that came the role of secretary,
then came the role of leader,
and then came the role of expert.
For the role of...
Regarding the role of system management
I will go to the management role first.
For each of you who have been in charge of a farm,
You will have to do this part very carefully
because if you don't, it will go wrong.
Of course, the original version
can still go and I will adjust it for you,
but if you can do it
right from the beginning,
it will still be better.
That is, you will be part of the unit.
Khanh Hoa, I see that I have not created
all the ministries here,
but in all the provinces across the country,
I have created all the ministries here.
To do what? First of all,
from the party committee down
to the ministries, to the ministries,
and the documents will also be sent to the ministries,
to the first ministries, for example.
When you go to the ministry,
you hold your phone,
There is also a document,
but it is not printed on paper.
That is also one thing,
and it is also a transfer of numbers to the departments.
For example, in Hanoi,
you have created a very complete part of it.
At the beginning,
I just do these steps first,
then I will go to part 2,
where I create units.
The way to create units is like this.
You go to the management menu and unit management.
Yeah. How to create a unit management,
you go to the unit management management menu.
This is the unit management menu,
and when you create a new one,
you will go to the plus button
to add a new one. You click Add New
at the right corner of the screen.
Here, you will enter the name of the unit.
For example, here I will have the building boards,
some units will have a political center, right?
Then I will enter the political center.
For example, I will not stay.
This is the political center of Cam Danh, for example.
And you can enter the official date.
You can enter the official date
from the time you come back.
But don't enter from tomorrow to the next day
or the next day or the next day.
Please don't leave it
because I am working on it.
I will enter the name code
of the political center.
For example, the name code
of the political center is A00.00.
For example, the real name code
of the political center is A00.05.
I can't get it.
When you enter the code into the system,
you will be notified
by this national telecom.
There will be an API sent
to the telecom that will notify this unit
to use the code
sent to the telecom on the party's business management software.
However, with the previous condition,
you have to cut the name code
that has been published on the old Iofit software,
for example,
which is being published in the Khánh Hoa love book.
And then what?
For example, if you enter the number 1,
it will appear on the party building board.
If you enter the name,
it will appear on Cam Danh Ward.
You don't need to enter a lot of structure words.
If you want to register
for the National Registration,
you will enter this part.
However, I will not encourage you to enter this part
because it is not possible
to send a lot of documents
to the Registration Office after entering.
You can only enter once for the administrative
admin of the province.
Then you click on "Save".
You chose the father unit,
which is the Party of the Indifference Party.
You can save it.
then there will be a unit It
was created in the Party Committee of Cam Ranh Ward.
This is the political center of Cam Ranh Ward, right?
And that is the unit management part.
The new way is like that and the new details
are like that.
When it comes to managing users,
you will go to management and managing users.
Next, I will create a clip
and then I will delete it Next,
you will go to the user management section,
which is also the same
as the unit management.
You will have the new plus section.
Please note that here
I will guide you carefully
about the user management section
because the personnel come in
or the personnel do the transportation, etc.
will be managed by the management
of the district office.
You will add a new user. For the leaders,
it is customary for you to enter the citizen
registration of the leader.
You have to enter the name of the school.
For example, I am Nguyen Thi Thu Trang,
so I enter Nguyen Thi Thu Trang.
must enter when you enter here
is the name is written normally,
the system will automatically specify
the flower
and when you sign up for this leader,
you have to put the name
correctly like this,
then the AI will catch the correct signature of the leader.
The password is that you have to put 1 number 2,
it's small, it's big, This is the end of the user management part.
Next is the user discrimination part.
One person can do many roles.
For one person to do one role,
then you leave one role.
For example, this is the leader
and the deputy secretary of the party committee.
For example, you put it like that
and you put the original unit
and you don't choose to receive the unit document
because the party will have a document
to receive the unit document
and transfer it to the leaders.
As for the users, the head of the units,
the building board also has a document.
If the unit does not have a document,
the unit's document
will be included in the management.
For example, if the building board, the agency,
the inspection committee,
the national defense committee
and the office all have documents,
then you will not enter the management part.
As for you, for example,
the document of the party committee
and the document of the office,
The main role of the staff is the office staff, right?
then you can let the experts
Now you choose the original unit
in this expert section
because this expert member is the original unit of the member.
And the role of literature is just experience, right?
And it is also not absolutely not selected in This
is the unit version.
Because if you choose to preside here,
the document is not about the unit's document,
but about the individual
of the member of the document.
I see that in many units,
the admin is placed like this.
This morning, I have a list,
I see that the district committee members,
most of the functions of the document
are being left to preside.
Then you guys delete this presiding
to help me.
Because when the letter receives the document,
I will talk more about it later,
it will not be in the unit's document,
but it will be in the personal document.
For example, today this student is a letter,
but tomorrow the other student is a letter,
today Mr. Trang is a letter,
tomorrow Mr. Tai is a letter,
then I just need to add Mr. Tai here
and I create a role for the letter,
I will still receive the old
and new unit document of the unit.
Anyone who gets out of this role
will not see it anymore.
Those who have entered the personal version
for the role of a professional
or a leader will stay with me forever.
For example, today I am the deputy director of the room,
I received 1,000 copies.
Tomorrow I will be the head of the room,
I will still receive
the new copies of the head of the room
and keep the old copies
of the deputy director of the room.
As for the unit's copy,
anyone who is the expert of the unit
will see it and get out of that role
will not see it anymore.
There will be a difference between the unit
and the individual version.
After that, we come to You can save it.
If your username is already on the system,
you can save it
and the system will tell you
that the username
is already on the system.
If you are creating new users,
you can save it here.
That's how to create a new user.
Give us a look.
The most important thing in creating a new user
is the structure of the unit and role.
Look, don't you know?
For example, in the future,
you will add more party members, right?
Vân Vân, then another deputy secretary,
at the same time as the secretarygeneral of the ministry or party, right?
Then I will be a person
who has many roles.
This system is also a strong point.
Different from the previous system,
you will not have to change roles here.
Change each role one
and every time there is a version
to a specific role, I see the roles
that I have to change,
I have to change over
and over again to see.
Now, the system that has many roles
will be displayed here.
That is a new step for users.
For example, in this morning, you guys...
that the rooms will not have a letter,
then you will form a directive
to receive a copy of the unit as your room.
As for the members of the Ward Council,
later, if any of the agencies
have children units,
for example, the previous day
was the National Assembly, for example,
in this there will be the population,
for example, the population units
will have a young secretary, for example,
then the secretary
will receive a copy of the As for the Committee of the Committee of the Committee of the Committee of the Committee of the That
is the opening of the system
and the management of users.
For the management of the unit,
for the management of the field,
I will also go through it
for you to see a little bit.
And you have some suggestions for the unit.
However, I also rely on a The most basic of all the provinces
in the country and the central government,
I have already shaped it for Khanh Hoa,
both coming and going of the Party
of the commune and the states.
For example, Luong Van Man Den, the commune party,
I am shaping here.
Here I am shaping all the communes,
I have 6 communes and 1 district.
However, later,
if any of the communes want to separate,
Why do you want to separate
and why do you want to share with the management of the office?
If you want to share with the management of the office,
please separate the fields.
I will pull the circle down
and I will shape the unit.
Note that the unit does not have a role and service form.
And I give the definition of this letter to which notes?
The back is the square notes,
so I will add them here.
I give the letter and define the roles inside this square note
and choose the path for those notes
And you can see that the letter
is being transferred to 123456, right?
Now you guys said
that the letter was not selected to the professional,
that is, this line,
this line to the professional.
I will delete it and save it as "Van Thu
will not see it".
And now I'm still letting
Van Thu see the members.
Candela Luongo Gardens, we can be you.
For those of you who are not familiar with it,
it should not be affected.
Because with these cells,
we have some rules. Those are the notes
that we have drawn,
but when the data is running in reality,
we cannot delete them.
We cannot delete them
because each of these notes
is born as an ID. When you add a new note,
you will see how many notes it will be.
It has all the numbers.
It's called a pair of shoes with numbers.
I will not delete this one.
Because when the letter
was sent to Mr. Tranh Van Phong of the Party,
it was in this note number 1.
I deleted it,
I gave birth to a note number 22 again,
then the version did not jump from number 1
to number 23. So I don't delete,
but I delete this action,
I delete it comfortably,
I save it comfortably.
Then I want to change,
when I don't want to change, I delete it.
When I want to change, I open it up,
I add it. What?
Then you can delete it easily.
Because the note is digital,
but the action is not digital.
So some of the rules
are not familiar to me.
Later, if you delete it,
the office worker will not see
anyone to change
because I have been deleted.
It will be back to zero on the system
That's about the land management.
If the administration runs on the same field,
it will be reasonable for the administration of the province.
In the whole country,
there must be a province
for the administration of the province.
That province is welltrained.
Some provinces have their own fields.
But after that,
the leader has to go back to the common field.
In my opinion, you should put it together
and you will manage it.
That's the management part.
There is one more part in the management part.
That is, you will sculpt the image management part for the user.
For example, the leader of my ward,
Mr. Bi Thu, Deputy Bi Thu, for example.
Here, Mr. Bi Thu,
please help me with the number 10. Uh huh.
you will always go to the top of my room
and always face the chiefs down here.
Or you can put the number 15 too. 15.
And the vice presidents will put the number 16.
I will leave this for you,
but you can also leave it,
but I will follow this rule.
All other rooms are the same, Mr. Bi Thu.
is 15. The vicechairs will be number
16 There are some communes
that have experience like this,
so you guys are right to sculpt
like this What are you guys
doing with the number of people who use it?
So that the deputies and vice deputies
must always be above the leaders?
Yes, for example, the office leader is in this,
I am leaving the members as number 31,
then later it will always be below the members.
As for the members of the staff,
please leave it as it is.
This number is very large, I was born,
the system will automatically like this
and it will automatically arrange the alphabet,
but whoever I type the number,
it will only change the number
and I will change it according to a general rule
for the whole province.
If so, it will be true in all cases.
That's how to create a user profile
and you will have to enter to create a signature for the leader.
For example, here, the secretary of Cam Ranh Ward
has no signature.
The management will usually be the one
who creates the signature for the leader.
Then you will choose a signature.
A signature that has already been cut.
If the signature is suitable
and has the PNG design and the white background
has been removed, you will paste it in
and you will write it down here.
So either the leader or the user
can go to their personal profile.
After that, there is also a new signature image.
However, with the leader,
the management or the office usually have to support, right?
I will create a signature.
The next step is to create a logo for the letter.
The manager can create a logo
for all units of the unit.
For example, if you are the manager of the office,
you will be able to create a logo
for the entire office.
For example, for the logo of the office,
you will create a logo like this.
And you will create two logos.
The first logo is the unit logo
and the second logo.
You go to manage the manager,
manage the logo image, can you see it?
If you don't have the unit number here,
you will add the unit number here.
If you don't have the confirmation number,
you will add the confirmation number here.
Usually, if you are a new unit,
you will add two numbers at a time.
You can choose any type of mode
and choose "only day"
to work I will add another one.
After adding,
I will create the image of this symbol.
For the unit symbol,
I set the height to 110.
The font and width are set to the same.
I set the image to the symbol.
As for the confirmation symbol,
I set it to 50 and 680 here.
If you tick something,
it will display the corresponding symbol here.
You put it like this,
it will match the mark on the water tank.
Or if you haven't put your signature in yet,
you can choose to add a new one.
And you choose these two characters.
This is the unit number. Confirmation.
I take the example
so I don't save it anywhere.
And I choose the type 1.
I choose the day of operation.
And you just have to reread it.
After that, it comes to the drawing of the mark,
as I just guided you.
Do you remember the standard of the mark?
After you have drawn all the marks,
I will make a rule
before you use the formal method,
and I will leave it for you.
And even if you cut the mark and it is blurred,
if you see any mark that is blurred,
it is not guaranteed on the computer,
I will also clarify it for you.
That is the shape of the mark.
Next, we will go to the structure of this logo.
Both Văn Thư and Quản trị Hệ Thống
can do it.
Văn Thư can also manage the logo
of the unit and manage the group.
Văn Thư will have these two parts:
managing the group
and managing the image of the unit logo.
I will show you how to create a group.
Go to group management
and add a new plus sign.
For example, you create a group.
the staff, the ward, the camp,
you will be a group. personal group,
this is the personal group, right?
And you add the individuals of the Cam Ranh Party
to have the versions that you send once
to a group and that's it.
You can choose to hug,
except for those who are usually late.
Can you give me an example?
then you will choose It would be a...
And you guys in the application area,
you can use it for yourself,
you create your own group,
or you use it for all units. If all units,
you will define which unit to use.
Organization here. no to you,
then you As for the next group,
I think the most important group
is the communication unit.
For example, 66... the People's Committee, for example.
Well... What do you think? Why do that?
For example, you are a communication unit, right?
And at this time,
you will choose all units of the People's Committee of the commune.
And you must know the name of the first time
so that you can find it quickly.
And you can find it by name,
I see that sometimes it is wrong.
For example, the People's Committee
sometimes has the People's Committee
to write the normal,
the People's Committee
to write the flower, right? Thank you.
You can't find it like this, right?
I have to hit it.
So I have to know the correct name,
and the code only has one address, right?
and teal.
I think it's hard to find this name.
I don't know. Ummm... Vibhanyin Zen.
Phuong, lay up. Phuong.
Cam Ranh here, right?
That's the name of the flower,
the name of the hair. Then you choose it.
You choose all the rooms.
This is the code. If you choose this code,
it will always come out.
Choosing a name is sometimes difficult.
Find a code that matches the name of the unit. Mwah!
Phuong Do Vinh.
For example, you create a group
and once like this, then you save it.
Later, when it comes to the part,
I will guide you to change the group like this,
it is very convenient.
This is the convenient part of the management
and the letter to create a group,
then I will guide you to the whole series
of the management part.
This is the group management.
Next, I will show you the main modules of the system.
including each role.
You just finished the management role, right?
Now I will come to the writing role.
I will go to the error path
that I just created.
Yes, please enter the email address.
On the screen,
you are looking at the main screen
of Mr. Van Thu. With the main screen
of Mr. Van Thu,
you will have the part of Van Van
waiting for the order to wait for the number.
Van Van comes to wait for acceptance
It will be different from other users
who have those two parts.
And other users will not have those two parts,
but only wait for the process to go down.
Everything is from waiting to processing
and to these areas.
Here, each user has a simple homepage.
If you want to see a simple
or complete page, you can see it.
And you will have your own personal profile.
And you will add a new signature. Wow.
That's right.
It's not that I have to take care of them more,
but I will be the one to do so.
You can choose the day of the event.
As you can see,
I have added a signature photo for myself, right?
Next, I am the secretary of the unit.
I will have two parts:
group management and unit management.
Group management I have just introduced,
and unit management management
I have just introduced from Mr. Quang Tri, right?
This is Phuong Cam Thanh.
Please note that when you add the letter of the Party
of the Republic of Vietnam,
He going to eat.
I pressed the button of the opposition party.
When you add a sign,
you have to click on the corresponding square
to create a square.
In this corresponding ward,
you just add the unit number
by the plus sign here.
If you do not add the number of the building board,
the agency will also come here
and the office will also come here.
For the office number,
you type it into the office
and you add the number.
That is, which unit number must be typed
into the corresponding unit to add.
Like... Please click here
and add the office's logo. Huh?
For those of you who are the management of the party,
you will be able to add it like that.
If not, you can add the letters of each unit.
If you attach only your letter to this unit,
you will only display each unit
to add a mark. There are many ways for me
to do management.
I can guide everyone or you.
For example, in the administration,
you are an admin,
you will create a profile
for a member in the office.
of this unit of the National Defense Committee,
then you will enter the system
and you will only see each unit
to add this part. Next, on the homepage,
you can see that there are all the modules like this.
You can enter from the text module
to all like this. It is also the same
as the text module here.
Normally, you will go directly
to the system part.
Here, you can see that the text is waiting . . . .
This is the sixth row. As you can see,
if there is an internal version
from other units sent to me,
then in the party body sent to me,
for example, the party party sent me . .
That's it.
How will you receive the communication board?
I have two sources.
The communication source is here.
The paper source will be added here.
The communication source will be added to the +.
You will receive As you can see,
we will be able to delete
all the information in the online version,
but the internal version
will not be deleted
because the internal version
is the only one on the whole system.
Therefore, we are following the 204 plan,
which is to save on DB,
on the infrastructure,
on the power supply.
For the online version,
from other systems and from other servers,
when it comes to me,
it is my own version, right?
then I will be deleted.
And the internal version
from other units sent to me
is not my original version,
but I only receive one original version, right?
And we are the original unit,
so we have the right to delete that original version,
and I will not have the right
to delete it for the internal version.
The internal version will be deleted.
As you can see, Lien Thong sometimes doesn't give you the type of the document.
In this case, you won't be able to log in.
You have to choose the type of the document.
You have to read the document
and know the type.
I will have to choose "Cong Van" here
and you choose the address of the address,
the number of that address
will jump out of the address.
And the way to create another address of Van Thu,
I will talk about this part first.
The way to create a document,
you go to the title section,
go to the title section of the document,
and you will add a new document here.
Here, for example,
I added a new test document
to the Let me look at the paper for you.
1 year or 5 years,
you choose the type of year, right?
And you enter the version of the notebook.
For example, on the 15th,
you run the real thing.
On the 14th, you go to the number... 550,
then for example,
you type in the current version number
so that when you enter the system,
it will start from the number
to 551 and then continue.
And you guys, please resign in.
select the operating unit for this table,
this table will be the table
of The Party is in a state of war.
You can rewrite it.
That's how you create a single folder.
Usually, there is only one folder when you come.
When you leave,
you can divide it into multiple folders
according to your own decision.
Or you can create a single folder.
It depends on your mission.
You can create one or more folders
You have to choose the right type of bamboo to eat.
According to that task, 1 year or 5 years,
usually I will do 5 years, right?
And I choose, I choose, I create a test,
then I create 1 year for it to be fast.
Then you guys in the D version
of this notebook to the number 200, then for example,
1999, the next will be to get the number 200,
then you will type the current number
that you just entered the notebook of the evening of the 14th.
There, and in the D version,
it will have 2 forms.
The first form is that you take a total of 1 notebook.
but they are different types,
then you will type in the number level
according to the type. And for version 5,
you enter the number 5,
the report comes to number 77,
then you type in the number 77,
the instruction comes to number 15,
then you type in the number 15.
When you go to the version of this book,
and this type will jump to number 6,
this type will jump to number 78,
and this type will jump to number 15.
Then you will shape it like that.
If you want to create a test folder,
you will create a common folder like this.
For those of you who save many different types of folders separately,
you create many folders, right?
And you don't give the number
according to the type,
but you give the number
according to the folder,
then you put it like this.
I just showed you
how to create a notebook.
And when the system that you have created a unit
is the Party, of different units.
That's the "Documents" section.
When you click "Accept",
you will see that when you accept this document,
you select the "Documents" section.
This is the "Office" section.
If you send it to the office,
but you haven't created a "Test" document for the office,
it will not display.
For example, this one.
This one is also for the office.
Nothing for the piano.
Because I have just created an activity unit as a unit.
For example, I have created a folder for this one
and there is a test folder,
then I will enter the folder like this.
And the current number will jump to the next number
and you will click to receive the mark, right?
And for those of you
who enter the folder by paper,
you will enter the plus sign here.
The first thing you need to do
is to connect to the scan machine
and install the driver of the scan machine.
Put the file into the scan machine and click
Scan File.
The system will return a driver file connected
to the scan machine
and the system together.
You will download it and install it.
It only takes 2 steps to complete.
For those of you who don't have a scan machine,
you can go scan somewhere else.
If you scan the file,
you can select the file.
If you select the file,
the AI will put all the parameters in,
as I introduced last time.
If you are the secretary of two units,
you will only select the unit
for you to enter the test.
For example, here I have a test here, right?
If you type the number 550,
it will continue to 551.
There is one more thing
in creating this notebook,
which is when you want to enter the default,
then you type in the default letter,
you guys write it down. Right.
When you guys... Go to this unit.
then the notebook will automatically put you in
and you don't have to choose.
That is, if you have a few notebooks,
you should put them in a certain place.
And it will be placed in the menu for you
so you don't have to click to choose.
If you have many different types of paper,
you should not put it in a certain place.
Let me add this tail
so that I don't have to worry about the name.
It looks like the real name.
You can see that the OCA of AI
will automatically drag the fields in, right?
You just choose the individual or unit
that you transfer to.
You can see that I am choosing to the members
of the committee and the leaders.
And I have not designated to transfer to a professional.
This is a different role,
not a professional one.
Do you have many members in your party?
There are a lot of them.
For example, I see that there is...
Ah, this is Mr. Ted.
Later, please arrange the leaders
to the top of the screen.
Let's avoid the number 31.
All the rural and rural areas
are following the same rules.
After you have entered the document,
you can choose to transfer it to the office
of the test ward.
I will try to rewrite it.
I have successfully entered the paper.
As you can see, the system will notify you
that you have successfully entered the folder
and when you enter the folder,
it will go to the folder
that has been processed.
And as I said earlier,
many of the members of the Party
and the Municipal Party of Phuong
are letting Mr. Van
Thu preside over the draft.
The draft will not be included
in this unit draft,
but will be included in this individual draft.
And if it is included in the individual draft,
it will not run in line with the line
that the administrative admin is shaping.
"Đến đã xử lý" . As you can see,
in the real notebook,
there are 9 text files,
and in the test file,
there is 1 text file.
And here you have the right
to view the notebook,
or view the group of types,
or view the file according to time.
Now I will log in to the user of Dong Chi Chanh office.
Yeah, they have got the fair.
I am working with many users,
so I will have to log in many times,
but you only have to log in once.
In 30 days, you can see that Mr. Tranh,
I have guided you to enter the document in two ways, electronic and online, right?
Now you will enter the document
and transfer it to the leader.
Now I will guide the leader
to process the document.
The leader will see
that there is a document waiting to be processed. . . . . .
I will click directly on the "Come"
button You can see that the leader
has received a document
that is dark black, right?
When a leader reads this document file,
it will be light black.
And with other systems,
I will have to turn off,
go out, and change. With the new system,
I will be able to change it here.
Or this is a conclusion announcement,
you will create a task here.
For example, I go to a transfer tree.
I'll let you guys
make your comments But every time you enter,
you have to enter like this,
it's a bit of a waste of time, isn't it?
Then you can put this opinion
in Let's create some models.
For example, I choose these two models,
then every time I choose, I switch.
When the office manager comes to work
or is sitting in a meeting,
you will select the model
and operate it on mobile or iPad.
I don't have to type anymore, right?
Sometimes I can't follow the meeting,
for example, then I choose the model,
I change it,
it will only be 3 times click,
it's very fast, right?
And if you give the processing time
here to the professional,
then later when the professional
will have to perform before this time
and it will perform KPI according to this processing time.
As for the leader who does not submit
the processing deadline,
the expert always performs within the deadline.
It's just that it has not been performed
within the deadline
or it has been performed within the deadline.
It has been completed within the deadline.
If there is a processing deadline,
it will assess KPI.
If this deadline has not been performed,
it will be that it has not been performed
beyond the deadline.
If the deadline has been completed,
it will be that it has been completed beyond the deadline.
and you will transfer it to the staff
or the leaders who can come to the office
will transfer it to the deputy
secretary of the office
to ask for advice, right?
This is where I will enter the samples
as "ask for advice" What for we do, Momma?
For example, I would like to move down to the expert page quickly.
For the leader who has accepted the request for the answer,
the member who has accepted it
must want to complete this document,
want to complete this task,
the leader must have a document to answer.
If the leader does not accept the request for the answer,
then I just need to report
that the task is completed and I will add the draft
if I want, or I will add the draft
if I want.
I will switch to the 9th channel to perform.
That is the leader when receiving a document,
then for the leader to deliver the document,
it will also go to the document
that has been processed.
And here, if the leader sees that the leader
has delivered it wrong,
then the leader goes to the document
that has been processed
and the leader goes in to see the details.
And the leader has a part here,
the list has been sent, I sent it,
and the list is sent to other people. .
with the main lines here, right?
Or you can see this list as well.
If you are familiar with the form,
you can see it in that form.
If you are familiar with the form of the map,
you can see it in the form of the list.
Here you can see all the properties of a document.
You can download it or print it out.
Or for this document,
you want to verify whether the document
to your department is correct or not.
As you can see here, the system has determined
that the digital certificate status
is effective
and that the digital certificate
is correct for the Government Digital Information Port
and is not changed
and approved at the time of registration.
This is a complete digital document.
As you can see, this is the paper version
of the government library.
You can see the red and black letters,
but it will have a confirmation mark.
This is the part that I have just shown you,
adding a new confirmation mark.
One is the unit mark,
the other is the confirmation mark.
This is the confirmation mark.
And below this will be the unit layer.
Oh. Is that right?
The unit number is locked in the part of the registered leader,
and the confirmation number is locked in that part, right?
And when the leader wants to withdraw,
there is a withdrawal button here.
If the leader transfers to many people here,
then the leader will have a withdrawal button for all.
Or withdraw 23 people,
then click on 23 people,
then click on withdraw here.
If there is 1 person here,
then it will click like that.
I will go back to the user of the staff member
and I will guide the staff members
to perform all the operations.
For the leader,
just receive the document and transfer
and hand over the document,
there will be a part
that is more compact than the professional.
And of course, the leader who wants to carry out
that document is also okay,
just like a professional.
yeah yeah The leader
or the expert receives a message
waiting to be handled here, right?
Then I click directly on it.
As you can see, when there is a task,
it will appear here, right? Huh?
Number 2373, you have just transferred from the office
to the professional worker.
As you can see,
the experts here will be able to perform
in this quick action code.
Or the experts will enter the In the details section,
it will be full of more notes.
I will explain each note for you to see.
For example, here, don't just take this one,
but want to attach a separate tag so
that later you can find it easily.
Then you attach a separate tag.
This is important, for example.
That's right. Some of you often mention
that this is important.
This is very important.
And then normal, etc. Click on "Record".
You have marked this document.
It is important.
After that, you search for the tag.
The important thing is that all the documents
you are pasting are important.
Just like you pasted the tag on Facebook.
Next, this document is an invitation.
You will create a meeting.
This document will be the summary
of this meeting schedule.
For example, this is the invitation
from the province of Uy
to the meeting today, right?
And the local authorities will enter the schedule for the leader, right?
And the participants will enter the schedule
like that,
then you will explain more carefully
about the schedule.
The next step is to save personal documents.
You can create a list of titles.
The title of the title is "Title" Tình nguyện gửi,
văn bản tình nguyện chẳng hạn.
Then you enter the recorded content
and you click on the record button,
then you will see that
after saving the personal documents,
you will turn it off.
After saving the personal documents,
you will see in the personal documents section,
I don't want.
And you want to find the titles
that you are looking for, right?
that you are looking for?
Another title is the office version
of Tinh Nguyen.
For example, you have created
these two titles
and now you are looking for the office version
of Tinh Nguyen, of course, it will not be seen anymore, right?
Right, let's go go.
All of them come out, right?
That's the personal layout.
It's like a green folder.
A 3storey, 2storey, 1storey folder.
You usually put it where you sit, right?
Who does administrative work,
You can see that when you click on the tag,
all the tags will be on the top.
And when you search for the important tags, Yeah.
There are two versions, right?
One is just an important one.
These are just some of the important versions
that you need to take note of.
This is a way for each person
to save their own letters.
You can find the search engine in any page.
When you open the search engine,
you can search from the beginning of the month to the end of the month.
There are many versions
that I have received.
You can open the search engine to search.
When you don't search for the search engine,
you can search quickly.
There are three search areas.
The first one is here.
The second one is here.
And the third one is here.
There are four search areas.
And the third area is in the search
for improvement, the fourth area.
This is the first area.
This is the second area.
This is the third area.
And this is the fourth area.
For example, here I am looking for the version number 2373.2.
I can search like that.
I want... I still remember some of those signs,
even though in the finished version,
after a few months of use,
there will be a lot of versions, right?
I can search quickly here
or search quickly here.
Uhhuh Quickly here, if you type the number,
it will only find the correct column
of this symbol number.
If you type the correct column,
it will find all 4 cases
of the symbol number,
the type of the text, the content,
the ID of the text,
and the person who signed it.
It will be in 5 conditions like this.
Back to Mr.
When you receive the document number 2373,
you will have the task to save the documents, right?
When this document belongs to the field of documents
that you are in charge of,
you will save the documents and on the side of the list of documents,
you have created the list of documents to save,
then now I will collect the documents in the list of documents, right?
If you don't have it,
I will you will add a file from this page.
It's the same as the file management module here.
Add a file link with each other.
This file list is for you to add a file,
right It's the same as when you go to the file list module
and add a new one. After adding a new one
to the file list,
you will put these templates in.
It's the same as when you choose
the template and save it in the file.
The next one is the most commonly used action.
What is it?
It's the report completed when you have finished it.
I have a phone,
so the internet is a bit slow.
When you have finished reporting,
you will click "Finish".
In case you do not have the function of your task,
you will return it, right?
I have already guided you to the processing document.
I will see who will transfer the document.
And when you click "Finish",
You will enter the content of the report
to complete and you can choose
the attached file
or choose the answer document if you want.
As for this document
that the leader handed over to me, for example,
Tránh Văn Phòng handed over to the specialist
who has a request to answer here,
there is the word "Có" here.
When you click "Finish"
the answer sheet will be required
to have a red star here.
Because there is an answer request,
there must be a "Go" sheet to be issued.
Answering the question,
we can complete the question.
Next, you will have two most commonly used ones.
You will usually use this one to see
if the document is 1, complete 2, create a draft
is 3, create a draft of the version is 4,
because the experts will not transfer to anyone else,
so they will not use the transfer of the version.
Some of the useful features are this head.
And the parts to execute the version
will be in the next section.
So now I will go in and create a draft
from this document to register the document.
I will always guide you
to go through the document, right?
Here, you just click on "Create a template",
then the template will automatically come to you.
It's also similar to the case where you will choose
from the page
and you will choose the page to answer.
The same goes for documents.
Not only we can use AI,
but all experts can use AI.
That's the automatic information transfer part.
You choose a document,
you create a document outside, right?
The system will automatically OCA the document.
Come in here, can you see?
Then you will sign up to the office
to avoid the office.
Please note that there are two phases
and phases that I will guide you carefully.
One is the phase, the second is the phase.
What is the phase?
When you sign up to avoid the office
to sign up to publish the document.
then you will choose to sign,
and if you choose to cancel,
then go to the top, choose again,
then you choose, right?
And here, this part of the form is that office members
can also sign that they are on leave.
I will turn off this part.
There will be a note.
This is just a miracle. Here it is.
Trinh Nguyen, the office manager.
It's not right here yet.
There are two of them.
It's just the rupture.
The rupture is the next step.
The rupture is coming down to Van Thu.
I have to leave the rupture here.
Hey. I will create a new draft
and select the draft again.
This lady here, I will... Select the office worker.
Here you can see that the registration will be stopped here, right?
When the registration will be issued by the office
or issued by the head of the party,
then at that time
When you sign, the office will select the unit to be issued
as the party or the office.
If the office is wrong,
the document can also be edited,
so you don't have to worry
that if you choose the wrong office,
it will be turned off.
And if you sign up on the regular basis,
you choose to review,
then this place will light up, right?
You have two ways to edit.
The first way is that you just like this,
you edit, press the edit button,
and then the office
will choose which deputy secretary
to sign up for.
Or you can choose from the beginning.
And if you choose the wrong one,
you can also choose again
to avoid the office. Don't worry,
the system is very open.
I will guide you more carefully later.
You can choose like this.
you will sign, right?
Of course, this is a simple form of registration,
but in fact, there may be many documents
that you have to sign
and have to ask for advice
from many people, right?
Then the "ask for advice" part here,
you can ask for advice
from the deputy secretary of the office.
At the same time,
here you have two actions.
The first action is to ask for advice.
The second action is to sign.
What is asking for advice?
When you click on asking for advice,
it will point to this area.
And when you click Sign in,
then it will go to this whole area
and this whole area means
that both sign and ask for an opinion
and the person who signs these two people
will not depend on the person who asks for an opinion.
If you press the sign button,
In other words, the main action
is to sign the contract,
and the person will be able to receive the consent
for the consent.
If you want to submit an opinion,
it means that you have submitted an opinion first,
then you have just signed it.
When you submit an opinion
to Ms. Truc Giang,
she will give you an opinion
and you will complete this draft.
At this time, if you click on submit an opinion,
the draft will be saved like this.
It will automatically save it like this
and it will be in the position of asking
for an opinion here.
And when you give your opinion,
In the description,
Ms. Truc Giang gives her opinion below.
Ms. Truc Giang gives her opinion.
If you have an opinion,
it will be in this area.
And when you have completed the reservation,
you will go to the registration button here.
You go to fix it, then change the new file
if you have changed, right?
Then you click register.
And the fact that you register,
it will go to both areas.
I will skip this part of this opinion
so as not to come to the real account of Ms. Giang.
If you click register,
it will be like that. And for those of you
who have the main action,
but in the Central Chamber of Commerce
and in other provinces,
it is often used to save
and create a receipt.
That is, this contract,
you are handed over
and created a contract. However, you,
with the order of the unit, must
If you want to register with a receipt,
you have to use the function to rewrite
and recreate this receipt,
then it will go back to the page.
You guys go to my receipt.
If you save this document,
Then you go to my checklist,
you create a checklist,
you will enter all these information fields
and you choose the draft
that you have just saved.
This is a straight line that you create.
to create a review.
If this happens, it will take two steps.
Instead, we will do it quickly,
which is to rewrite and create a review.
The system will automatically link
to a review menu
and will automatically link all the specific fields of this draft.
Here, right?
The whole review registration part.
You can sign in,
but I don't have USB today,
so I'll leave it on the side.
You can send it.
Comrade Phò Bì Thư, Thường Trực, right?
Tang Yifeng.
As you can see, the name "Cam Ranh"
will appear here. There.
I added a new political center unit,
I put Phuong Cam Ranh, right?
Here is the old unit that you created,
the party of Phuong Cam Ranh,
you are putting Cam Ranh.
Later, if I want to fix the word Phuong Cam Ranh,
it will have an additional part here.
In the evaluation part,
it will be filled out like this.
When you click to save the process,
you only have to enter
the sent information
and the summary information, comments, and so on,
then the following documents,
then the comments,
This is a sample of the approval
of the Central Government.
The whole country will follow
and the part to whom,
that person will display the signature of that person.
For example, when you log in to the office,
you will only display the signature here.
When you log in to the deputy
secretary of the committee,
you will only display it here.
Then you will do the same thing
as before As you can see,
the person in charge
is Mr. Tranh Van Phong, right?
The person in charge
will be able to monitor all the fields
that you are in charge.
Now I will go to the office.
And I'm just changing the... After uploading,
you can see that the expert
is editing a edit ticket to the leader, right?
Then it will be in the edit ticket menu.
And now I will edit Wait,
let me cut the image. Yeah. At that time,
I edited it by the draft,
but I rerecorded and created the draft, right?
There are also drafts that you will edit
directly from the draft
and no longer rerecord
and create the draft.
I will create another file
and I will delete this title
for it to be different.
I am taking the same version
I also choose to go to Mr. Tran Ngan
Phong's office to review.
and select "Sign in" Click "Sign in" As you can see,
Mr. Tranh's office
will receive a document waiting for processing.
One is waiting to be processed,
and the other one is waiting to be processed.
It depends on the nature of each document
that you will perform different actions.
For example, when you are sure with the document,
you are just checking the signature,
then you check it directly
with the document and check it directly.
And you have to ask for advice from the leaders,
other units,
or the leader requires that all the documents
must be checked through the checkbox,
then you check at the checkbox.
For checking at the checkbox,
the leader will check directly at the checkbox.
The manager will go in and read this.
When it comes to the professional role,
you see in the editing section,
the manager has already read it, right?
I just read it, Tránh Văn Phòng
has just read it.
Then you will follow the reading status.
Here, the reading mode.
Here, the office manager has read it.
Yes, but I haven't handled it yet.
I haven't handled it yet,
but I have read it.
And now I will browse in the office
of the office secretary,
what will be the status?
You have two ways,
you can browse quickly here
and you can enter your opinion here.
After you enter,
it will also go to this part inside.
Just like that,
and you can choose the file outside
or inside as well. And all these parts,
whether you enter it outside or inside,
it will also go down in this section.
The suggestion for handling is all down at the bottom.
If you want to redo it,
please click on the "Redo" button.
You can see that after redoing it,
it will go to the processing menu.
As you can see,
there will be an opinion section at the bottom.
And there is also a whole section below.
And now, here, the member has agreed, right?
And now, to the member, Phó Bí Thư.
I will also be able to follow
the same page with my fellow students.
Now, the person who is being handled
is Deputy Secretary Thu, not the office worker.
I will log in as Phó Bí Thư.
As you can see, Mr. Tránh Văn Phòng
has just approved the approval.
He will go to the processing part, right?
And now, Mr. Phó Bí
Thư has approved the approval,
he will go to the approved part.
That is, the last person will go to the approved part.
Mr. Bi Thu will receive the ticket here.
As you can see,
the procedure is the same as in the office.
I will also go to this section
and I will also enter my opinion
as quickly as possible in my section
and select the asylum file if you want.
And you click sign in.
Today I am giving the Central Library
also has a conference to borrow the USB,
so I don't need an USB to come back.
Then you guys click on the registration,
or you want to add someone else
to ask for an opinion,
then you guys, for example,
the deputy secretary said
that you need to ask for an opinion
on the secretary
or other deputy secretaries,
you can register here. Add more people.
Xin yi kien ở đây. Đúng ạ.
In the case of Mr. Tránh
Văn Phòng has already approved.
In Van Man Di, you have to continue to pass to Phaw Hi
Thu street. You have to pass quickly here.
or you can read the file.
There are many ways, but the most correct
and common way is to read the file
and do the analysis inside
because you have the content.
You read it, then you can do the analysis
or reject it inside, right?
And as I mentioned earlier,
you can change the signature of the office worker.
For example, this is not the field of this deputy secretary.
I will change the signature
to another deputy secretary,
then here you will click on the comment button
and click on the signature. Now I'm going to do the construction
without going to your account.
Here, you can see that after you sign the approval form,
I will leave it here.
So, the schedule will be in here.
And now I'm doing the "Luong Dua
Thao", right?
"Cafe Duyet Song" from the office.
At this time, there will be three versions
waiting to be processed in Phò Bi Thư.
As you can see, if the document is already read,
the color is dark, if it is not read,
the color is light black,
and if it is not read,
the color is dark black.
Usually, the leader will read this document file
and this is very important
and the departments will be stuck a lot.
As you can see, the system has announced
that it cannot determine the location of the signature, right?
Although I have entered the signature here,
but it is wrong.
For example, my name is Nguyen Thuy Thu Trang.
If it is Nguyen Van Trang,
it will not match the name
and AI will not catch
the right signature of me.
You have to put the correct name, Phó Bí
Thư Tết This is the name of my colleague,
I just put the name Tet,
but my real name is no one is the name like this, right?
Please read it. In the office picture,
if you see it wrong,
you can fix it online right away
or go to the leader, you can fix it,
or the person in the Thank you. ,
I just need a name without flowers,
it's here, you can see it right away.
The right name is the signature,
the signature automatically fills in here.
At this time, it's just a review of the signature,
it hasn't been approved yet,
it hasn't been designated as a signature,
it's just a picture of the signature
and it's automatically customized according
to the right definition of the standard of the standard of these brothers and sisters.
If a document that doesn't appear on the signature
For example, this document does not have the word "register".
But if you still want to register,
you still have a way.
That is, you click here
and you click on "register, sign up, add",
then you click on "add".
But I will not encourage this case
because it is clear that AI is mistaken for the name,
compared to the entry name,
then it will make a mistake.
And the AI usually catches this on 99%.
Except for these cases,
in addition to the Word version,
you can see the name
of the person who registered,
but in this part,
there is also the People's Committee of Khanh Hoa District,
but you have already covered that word,
but it is still a column in this signature,
it can never be on this signature. I don't recommend you
to pull your leg here.
When the signature is correct,
the leaders will come in, read it
and see the signature like this, right?
Viewed in my place,
it can be large or small,
depending on your preference.
After that, you will do the signature
here, right?
If USB is not plugged in here,
it will tell you that there is no suitable USB.
And if you plug it in,
this place will go to the bit4 table
and you will enter the code
of If you sign in,
you will have a successful registration.
That is for the leaders
that I have just guided you
to include both the "come"
and "go" documents.
The "come" document is the way to process the "come" document.
Receive the "come" document
and wait for the process.
How to transfer the process
and how to have the following benefits.
Plus the "come" document
to be transferred to the "done" document.
Plus the "go" document to be processed.
Here, if the leader goes to the "come" document,
Trang Chu, Van Man Di,
Chờ Sửa Lý is also Van Man Di,
Chờ Ký Duyệt. As for the pages
that have been implemented by the leaders,
they will be implemented.
If the leaders sign themselves
or the leaders of the higherups,
they will go to the leadership of me
to create the leadership.
Next, after the leader has finished signing,
I will guide you to the text field
to submit the number and issue the text.
Yeah, he going to.
When the leader has signed the number,
it will go to the "Waiting for the number" section.
I'm still waiting for the grade.
of Mr. Van Thu Here, my user is attached to the text
of many test units.
There are many versions.
You will click on "Wait for the number".
It is the same as the "GoAround" section.
There are a lot of documents
waiting for the level number.
There are three actions.
The first action is if this document is done
by the leader quickly in the operation,
but does not click here
and does not know that it lacks a signature,
then it will go down and it will not have
the signature of the leader.
Similar to this document.
Although the document is down,
there is no signature of the leader.
When this document is not appropriate, right?
Then the document will have two ways.
The first way is to return it to the leader.
And the second way is here.
This fellow has not signed
any documents yet. Add another document.
The second option is that
the leader can also go to the "Dã phê duyệt" section.
There is a "register" button.
For example, in this version,
the leader does not have a signature,
then the leader can click on "register"
and then go back to the processing field
to fix the correct name
or fix the content, etc.
There are many cases
where the leader has signed,
but there are 1 or 2 pages
that have not been fixed,
then the leader can go to the processing part
or have approved.
For middle leaders, for example, Mr. Tránh Văn Phòng or Mr. Phó Bí Thư, but they sign on Mr. Bí
Thư to approve the approval,
then Mr. Phó Bí
Thư is also in the processing.
Island located.
I will type it back to the person
who will receive it in the processing section of that person.
The second action is when
the leader is done signing,
but calls Vân Thư
and says that he will not publish it anymore,
or waits to publish another version,
it is wrong content, etc.
Then you will reject the number
and you will enter the reason for the rejection, right?
Next, you will perform the most common action,
which is the number action.
When you press the number,
you will choose this number Here, 1811.
You have two actions.
The first action is to enter the number.
The second action is to enter the number
and enter the password.
The second action is to enter the number.
Entering the number means that after entering
the number,
you enter the password and send it.
And the action to enter the number
is that you enter the number
and leave it in the menu
that has entered the number
and leave it there.
You haven't sent it to anyone.
You haven't entered the password
and haven't sent it.
I'm going to perform the first step,
which is to grade and fill in the form.
As you can see here,
the system will automatically view
the document number.
Please note that this first page
will not be available when you finish publishing.
Because this page is for the middleclass leaders
who have a list of opinions.
Then the leader will see
right on the first page
that there are those who are in the field
and have opinions.
Just for the sake of signing the list.
When the template is finished,
there will be no more pages left,
only this template. As you can see,
the number of template symbols
will automatically fill in, right?
So we're going to And as you can see,
the year is already there,
but usually if the season
is set to the old year
and the new year is set to the old year,
then you should practice the habit of not leaving the year
here so that when the system is automatically set,
it will automatically fill this year here.
For this table,
if it is appropriate and has the leader's sign here,
you will do it. If there is a signature,
you will pull the sign in here, right?
And for this table that has the subordinate,
including the number of workers,
etc. below, if you need a number,
you can click on the plus sign in this number.
This number here,
you drag it down to the number part.
of the date of the paper,
the day of the public, the month, etc.
You pull it in and you pull the sign
to close the gap line
at this corner, right?
Then you do the marking.
This is the electronic marking action
for the digital leader board.
After you finish marking,
it will turn on the popup screen
to see who you want to transfer.
Like this.
The popup screen will be the same as this one.
It will always turn on this screen.
This is... See,
it will turn on automatically
It will always turn on this screen
and you will forward it to individuals,
units and groups of units
or telecommunications units or telecommunications groups Then
you will perform, for example,
you choose individuals,
units in all parties,
or you choose the group
that you have created at the beginning of the management.
I will guide you to create a group.
For example, you choose this individual group.
For this group of individuals,
there are a few people,
you can... For example, normally the group will choose
to transfer to all four of them.
But you don't want to transfer
to the second member. The third one,
please click here.
Ah, it doesn't change here.
Then it will automatically crack like this.
And you click agree.
Although this document is transferred to this group,
it only transfers to the first and fourth candidates.
That's all.
And you enter your opinion and click enter.
Nếu muốn toàn đối với... You
can choose the telecommunication group here.
You have created a telecommunication group here.
Group 12S here, right?
Then you will create that group
and similarly for group 12,
you do not change for the first 5 units,
then you click on do not change,
then you will change for the remaining 8 units in the back,
right The advantage of creating a network group
is that we can create
a group that we can use forever.
And every time you use it,
you don't have to find each network code
or each name, right?
When you create a group,
you can see the network code of the units.
You don't have to find each unit anymore,
even though you only need to change one.
I don't need to remember the address of this Hanoi City Public Service Station, right?
I don't need to transfer all the employees here,
I just need to transfer them to the Public Service Station.
Or I go to this group, I see this address,
then I go out and choose a separate unit.
I find this address.
It's even faster if you have to check the address of the Hanoi Public Security Service.
then you can switch groups,
individuals and units
to use TAP again here.
Or you can use it on the transfer screen. Here.
That is the issue of the publication of electronic documents.
At this time, I have guided you to the part
that I will forward to the units and individuals, right?
For the units and individuals,
you will choose or group,
or to the mobile unit.
Besides choosing here,
you can type your name here to find.
And there is a problem
that I need to note for you guys.
That is, today I finished early,
then later you will have some operations
on the machine that you bring today.
Then you guys just do the operations,
I will do it with you guys.
And if you want something,
I will solve it. .
Completely different 92.525.
foreign foreign When it is published,
it will be sent to the document
waiting to be processed by the individual.
As for the documents
that have already been sent,
it will be sent to the individual
to be recognized.
That is, it will go into the same folder.
And you can see that the host and
To know, it will have a different sign.
The main character is CT.
To match, it will be PH.
To know, it will be in a separate row.
You can see that these are the main characters.
Wherever there is the word PH,
it is a match. If you have any questions,
please feel free
to ask them in the Q&A section below.
You will be issued with the digital document, right?
After the registration,
you will enter the number.
As for the paper document,
you will be issued like this.
You will enter the "Go" document.
This is the finished document.
Or you can go to the "Wait for the level" section as before,
then at the corner of this screen,
there is a new "+" section,
then you will perform the new "+" section,
and similarly to the "Come" section,
you will have Select the attached file,
and the system will automatically OCA the files.
but you only have to enter the operating unit and the folder.
Similarly, if you want to write a letter,
you have two options.
I choose to write a letter
You can change the direction from the "Go" folder to the "Publish"
folder here,
or you can go to the "Go" folder and wait for the level number here.
Then I will also go to the "Add New" tab.
I will choose a document
that the leader has just signed,
but I have not entered the number in the release.
That is, in this part of the document,
there are many cases, right?
There is the first case.
first is that you choose the version
that you have signed up for this number,
sign up on the outside
and then you put it in,
then the sign is the black one
and it will not be compatible with the electronic one,
then I will sign up for confirmation
on this corner, right? For this version,
but it is just signed up,
I have not signed up for the number,
I have not signed up for this part,
then I can completely put it in so
that I can sign up for the electronic sign up here
and I don't need to sign up for confirmation anymore.
A version only needs to be signed up for a sign,
it is confirmed.
For example, For example, if there is a page
that does not have
a red mark on the bottom,
then you can make a red mark on it.
Here you will choose the unit
for you to publish, right?
Depending on this page,
if you choose the unit,
you will be able to get the document, right?
Then I will choose and
I will choose the corresponding folder.
For example, if you choose TestD,
the system will always have Validate,
the next number in the folder is 200,
because when you enter the current number
of this test folder to number 199,
do you remember?
When it reaches number 200,
I will enter the number
200 here and save it.
As you can see, for the paper version,
it will be a little bit different from the electronic version.
If you click Save,
it will not turn on the screen
for you to choose to transfer,
but if you click Save,
it will go to the version
that has reached the number.
You have just saved a test number, right?
And you will, for this document,
if you are here, if you scan the document
that has a mark here,
you will make a confirmation mark on it.
Then you will do it like this.
You go in and close the confirmation mark.
This unit, I have not written a letter yet,
I will temporarily put a sign here.
Later, Nha Trang Party members
will go to fix the sign to close the door.
I don't know. I don't have a camera
to hide my face.
I'm going to take the password from the office
and I'm going to turn it off.
I will test it later.
I will go in and select "Confirm"
The first thing you do
is to create a code. For the unit code,
you put the image here.
And you put this as 110.
You save it and then you go to the template
to put the confirmation mark,
to put the entire image and information
and the number of signatures it
already has on the document,
then you don't need to fill in the number of signatures here, right?
If you leave the tick, you can sign it,
or if you want to display anything,
you can tick it up. If you have an email,
you can also tick it up. It's okay.
Number 50. I set 680 as the best size.
We have done a lot of research
and compared this size to the paper pattern
that you have drawn
and it will match with the signature.
I will mark it again.
The first mark is the unit mark.
For this table that is not hidden yet, I will close the mark here.
Can you see the number here?
It's blank, right?
Can you pull it in here for me?
Because this number,
can you see the blue line here?
There's a number hidden in there. .
When we go to PDF,
we don't see it, but in fact,
there is a number there.
We will drag it in.
And we drag the mark like this.
And we confirm that the marking is done.
That is the unit marking.
When we send this mark to the unit,
they will come in here
and they will verify that this mark
is the correct one of the unit.
Then it will be OK.
As for the unit authentication,
you will perform authentication.
For example, there is a red mark here.
You will pull this red mark
to come out here, right?
And you do the authentication like this
and it's done.
For two authentication tasks For each case, you have guided me very well.
I've explained it to you carefully.
As for the complete button,
sometimes you type in this,
but you type in this wrong, it's okay.
It will go to the version
that has been released.
Because you guys don't want to send it away,
you guys have a lot of copies, you guys
have numbered them and then you guys
put them in
and it's already published, right?
Not for anyone to change.
Then I still go to this menu,
I close the code
plus I change it as usual,
I send it away as usual.
This is the process of publishing
the paper version.
What is the process of publishing
the paper version?
From all of these menus,
you all have a plus sign.
When you have finished upgrading,
it will go to the upgrade.
After upgrading, you will find the version
that you have just finished working on.
And it often has a fault like this, guys.
For the paper, it often has a fault like this.
But I support the water,
so I listen to the phone a lot about this case.
I always guide you guys.
Let's take a look at one of the documents.
Later on,
our support team will definitely help you
a lot with this. I put this document in.
At the time of March,
August, it was the most interesting case.
Here, in this part,
you will usually put the number of your hand
and write your hand on this part, right?
It's the day, why is it August here?
Ah, March, but you write this number 3,
it's close to When
the AI receives this number,
it is the number 8. It's only March,
but the release date is August.
For example, here is 9/8.
Yes, the actual date of this document
is July 9th,
but it was received on August 9th.
The actual time is March 9th,
but you wrote the word.
Sometimes it's too beautiful,
it's stuck up. The AI will receive it.
If you don't fix it,
you will have to fix it.
you will have to save it.
Here, you will come here
and choose the number.
At this time, it will be 201, right?
I did it just like... If you are wrong,
you will not see that version here. Why?
Because it only appeared
here until August.
So you said that after I finished the grade,
it kept flying away.
That is a school that is suitable for the whole country.
Normally, you will find it here
and it will come out. Do you see it?
It will come out on August 8th.
Then you go in and fix it on the day
This is only the present.
It will only be displayed. If you go back,
you will see that it is always here,
but I still go back to the level.
As you can see,
it will be displayed on the right day.
Of course, the next day,
starting from tomorrow,
it will not be displayed,
because it will be displayed on the next day.
This is the case of the number
and the number of letters.
I have just shown you the menu,
the "come", "go" and "open" versions.
What is "open"?
If you want to open the version
for other people,
you will go to the "open" version.
For Van Van Di,
When publishing the document
or when entering the document
or when the document is published,
you also have a public document.
But when you receive it
and you want to publish it later,
it is also possible. It has all functions.
I still have my phone with me.
but I'll be chugging
You will go into the implementation,
there is a note
that reads the details of the document, right?
The 2373 document has just passed the test.
There is the public part of the document.
You go into the public section,
you will select the public area and you ... For example,
you can choose all the members in this office.
This is a guide to the version
from the central government
sent to the provinces
and then sent to the communes.
Instead of choosing to transfer the version to many people,
you can use the public function.
When you click on the record button,
it will go to the public version
of all users in the Cam Ranh District Office in this public version menu.
Thank you.
Similarly, there are two public versions here.
And next is the menu
You should take the responsibility first.
For example, Deputy Secretary
or Secretary of the Deputy Secretary Hello everyone,
welcome to my channel. As you can see,
this member has not been assigned
from the top leadership,
from the committee office,
from the committee,
or you have not handed over to any unit,
then you will perform
in the task management section,
the task list.
Here, you will perform new tasks.
and click "New". If you are a secretary
and you hand over the task to the leader,
you have to select the correct name
of the leader here, right?
Not the one who hand over the task to the units.
Enter the task.
and you choose the day of completion,
for example,
you choose the day of completion
until tomorrow to finish,
then this task will always tell you
that it is about to expire.
Here, you can choose individual or unit.
For example, I choose to hand over
to my colleague.
For example, I hand over to the unit,
which is the office is a personal colleague,
then it will be handed over
to the individual of this colleague,
then it will enter.
If you choose to hand over the unit to the office,
the office leader will see this task.
In the owner's section,
The leader of that unit
will look the same.
If this task comes from a certain version,
you can select it from the search icon to that version.
But Deputy Secretary, since this morning,
I created a new account,
so there is no new version. Okay.
For example, in this case,
according to the conclusion notice,
you will receive 3 tasks.
You will perform 3 more tasks here.
Task 2, Task 3. Hey.
Now, I will perform a task.
When you go to the main page,
you will see that there is always
a delivery service here, right?
And it's about to arrive. Hey.
and it's going to be this color.
Click on it and you will see the task
that I am delivering is coming.
I'm handing over to my colleagues.
And you can see below
the group of units handed over,
the group of units received.
or a list group like the one before. Right? See?
Or the same state as before. Here,
you are handing over to the office, right?
The main unit will be in the office unit.
And now if you go to the list of tasks,
I am delivering to a personal colleague,
it is not in the delivery task tab of this unit,
it is in the personal delivery task tab.
Let me do it again, task 2.
I will select "Personal"
I will do the same thing again.
I will do the same thing again
As you can see, it's not here, right?
Even though it's a new success,
it will be here.
It's a personal mission, right?
This is the second mission.
And when you go to the main page,
you will see that there are two missions.
One mission is in progress,
one mission is about to be completed.
Yeah. A task is being carried out,
a task is about to be completed,
a personal task is being carried out.
Now I will go to the comrade
and the unit to receive this task
to perform the operation.
This is the staff member
who received the task
that was delivered directly
by the deputy secretary, right?
Then you will have a task to receive.
In the morning, I created 2 tasks,
now 1 more task is 3 tasks. OK.
Nhiệm vụ này em vừa mới giao
đây đúng không ạ? As you can see,
my delivery time is 16:20
and I just made it.
Now you will have the update button.
For the task that you are not assigned,
you will only have three levels:
are performing,
closed proposal and completed.
As for the office worker,
I have 3 accounts in total Yes,
you see that the task of receiving
the unit is about to arrive
is the task that If
you have to finish the knife tomorrow, please click directly on it.
The mission received by the unit
will be in the unit tab,
the mission received by the individual
will be in the individual tab.
When updating the progress of the mission
that has a deadline,
you will have an additional deadline proposal.
Because if there is a deadline,
whether short or long,
it is close to the deadline.
If you have not completed it,
you also have a deadline proposal requirement.
For me, I will perform two tasks.
You can see that this is the task.
Nhiệm vụ của lãnh đạo giao này
and say Nghia Vu. Here you are.
Your mission is I'm going to hand over to the unit.
The deadline is coming, right?
As you can see, the deadline is from 9th to 10th.
Now, I will go to the office.
I would like to suggest that the deadline
is 31st and the result
is 50%, for example.
But I can't find them for help.
Nhiều đơn vị.
such as the board, the committee, etc.
You have to report in real time.
It depends on the beginning of the work.
After updating, then you can go
to the leader to open this task.
There will be a waiting section.
As you can see,
it is still on the 10th of July.
Now, if you refuse,
you will force the person
to be handed over.
The office will still have to follow this limit.
You can see that After finishing,
the line at July 10 will always jump to July 31.
Can you see that? It depends on the leader
whether he agrees to postpone or not.
And for those of you
who have received this task,
this task is no longer on the horizon,
but it is being carried out.
The horizon is still very far away.
And for this task,
this is the unit received,
the unit performed.
If the unit is already placed like this,
I don't know who is the main head
of this unit to perform, right?
Then you will perform the attachment of the head.
For example, I attached it to Mr. Tranh's office
for this test, for example.
Then it will always have the head to perform
so that Mr. Phó Bí
Thư knows who is handing it over.
You will do so.
Next, you will go to the expert,
you will update the progress of this,
it is completed. Nghe em hoàn thành thực
tế hôm nay chẳng hạn
If the update is complete,
you can add file or report. Click update.
Then I went to the deputy secretary.
Sẽ thấy một cái nhiệm
vụ giao đi cho cá nhân cũng sẽ
chờ phê duyệt. Nhiệm vụ giao đi,
nhiệm vụ giao cho cá nhân.
The test 2 is also waiting to be approved
and on the outside,
you can see that the specialist
has completed and has entered
If you have completed the task,
you can go to the task list
or the task waiting menu.
It will list the tasks
that are waiting for you to complete.
There are two actions here:
"Complete" or "Decide".
then I will enter the reason to refuse.
Of course, he had to go back
to that colleague and do it again, right?
It's about the implementation,
not the completion.
There was a completion task here.
Now, I would like to resume this task.
When it's done, it will close that task.
In fact, there are many cases like that, right?
At this time, the owner will have a task.
I have reported that it has been completed
and it is being implemented.
Now the leader has to cancel that task. Intervention.
At this time, this task is assigned to the staff, right?
And now it's time for the staff member.
That mission has been completed, right?
It won't be reacted At this moment,
the mission has been completed.
The leadership has decided
that it has completed the mission.
Next, as the leader,
you can see this menu.
According to the KVI business management,
as I said at the beginning,
with you as the secretary
and the general manager of the ward,
you will see all the members of the ward,
all the members of the ward
and all the members within the units.
About the situation of each member,
each unit, all the units of the Party.
Follow the unit.
According to the individual,
according to the unit,
or you can see it in the list.
That's statistics. and open the plus sign,
we will see the following 5 versions.
What are these four versions?
Here you can see that if the version comes
and the leader changes it If there is a limit
and the limit is too much,
the nonexecutive professional will ask Quá hạn chưa xử lý,
đúng không ạ?
Còn nếu mà chuyên viên hoàn thành đúng hạn
thì nó là đây ạ.
Và không giao hạn thì nó sẽ
là trong hạn mà chưa xử lý, đúng không ạ?
Có giao hạn mà quá hạn đấy
mới hoàn thành thì
nó sẽ là đề là hoàn thành quá hạn.
Many provinces and counties
are using this KVI menu
to assess the number of staff
in their provinces and counties.
Many provinces have implemented this.
Here, the leaders from the central government
can also see the same picture
from the central government
to the local government,
to the highlevel commune and subdistrict.
In addition, the system management staff can
the report.
As for the system management system of the commune,
it can also receive reports.
The report on the situation of handling the document of your unit
to make weekly reports.
For example, in Hanoi or some provinces or central provinces
every week, you will also use this report.
Here, we have a meeting
with the leader of the Central Committee Office of the Party,
Mr. Phó Chánh Hưng or Mr. Hải Ninh.
I usually have to submit this report
to see how the situation of handling
the transfer of numbers
in the Central Committee is like,
each department one by one,
then I have to submit this report
whether to use the whole process or not,
or sign it with a piece of paper
and then put it on the system, right?
And if there is a document coming,
is it processed or not?
Or is it all too late?
Or are there a lot of documents
that have not been processed?
We all use this report
to report to the leader during the meeting.
Every week, we all have to meet every Saturday.
It's been a while since the last report.
Can you see it? I'm not admitting
and they don't know what you As for the coming documents,
for example,
the organization has 48 coming documents
and only one document coming to the paper route.
And there are 11 online documents,
there are 36 documents
sent from the internal agencies of the Party, right?
I know everything.
For example, the Office of the Provincial Committee
has a total of 25 documents issued,
but issued 25 paper documents
because I was using secret documents
last time, right? Then this test unit,
you guys are testing,
so you guys use all the numbers,
so it's one hundred percent.
For example, at the time when Mr. Ngoc
came to Hanoi, he was very close
to this comprehensive report
and every week I had to print out
the report
that was for you to run the units,
you had to use all the numbers, right?
Which unit will be arranged from high
to low or from the bottom to the top?
Which unit is high
above or low above? BING! That's it.
The admin can see and submit the report
and choose from day to day within a month.
For example, from June 2nd to July 2nd,
we will automatically calculate within a month.
From day to day,
you can calculate one more week,
but at most not a month.
Then you submit the report.
As for the admin of each district,
they will be able to see each district
in the area above.
Those are some of the features
that I will introduce to you.
Next, I will introduce you to the management of the meeting schedule.
Yeah. You will go to the meeting schedule menu.
For users who have been shaped
as a meeting manager,
like the user at the beginning,
I guided you to shape the meeting management role menu.
there will be more menus than other members.
Other members only have these three modules.
These are the three main modules
that everyone has in the system.
As for other members,
there will be Those who manage the meeting
will have the structure, the output,
and the report of the meeting.
And the leader list, the official list,
and the meeting list.
What is this meeting list?
Everyone has to create a meeting list.
And the meeting list
will be who has the structure and role
of the meeting list. Here, for example,
I have a structure for the staff member.
foreign foreign foreign foreign Yeah,
but really hope.
The first thing you have to do
is to create the name
of the meeting rooms in your unit.
Then you go to the new tab
and create a meeting room.
And you choose the management meeting room, right?
Choose the owner unit of the party or the party office.
When you choose this owner unit,
it will go to the meeting room manager of that unit.
The meeting schedule. Here is the scale,
who goes to the real room,
whether there is a broadcast bridge or not.
Then you can do it.
For units that you don't want to have an extra schedule,
you just let everyone's meeting room
be automatically scheduled,
then it will automatically
But it will not be the right time
that I want to meet and follow
the leader's instructions.
then you will do it again.
When you create a meeting,
you click on the new meeting,
then you will choose the meeting
that you created here, right?
It will automatically display the meetings,
many meetings, many meetings,
it will display all of them here
for you to choose.
And you have a function that checks the time of the meeting.
For example, here there is room 1, room 2, room 3.
In that room, room 1 is all busy here.
Then you will not be able to choose here anymore.
And you just choose room 2, room 3.
The time is busy here.
Can you tell us about the topic of this meeting?
And you choose the time of the meeting, right?
We will meet at 5:00 pm.
The system will automatically set the time of 2 o'clock.
After 1 hour of meeting,
you will go to fix.
For example, if you study at your internal unit,
you will choose the management meeting room
and you choose the meeting room
of your unit to manage.
For example, if you are the mayor of Phuong,
you will go to the meeting room
of the city council office today.
For those who go to the meeting,
they are not managed, right?
And hit the meeting.
This is the second floor of the office, right?
And this meeting room,
when you type this meeting list,
it will type by itself, right?
Because I will go to class anywhere.
And if the meeting room is managed,
then I will choose the meeting room
from my own resources.
And you will choose the documents.
For example, today I have three guide documents.
4 instructions for you.
For example, this meeting schedule,
admin will create it from yesterday.
After that, after completing this meeting schedule,
you will be sent a message to the phone.
You will be invited to attend a meeting with this content,
at this time, this location, where, right?
And you open it, open it,
open it, open it.
the details of the meeting,
there will be this document
and the person in charge of the meeting
will want this document.
After the meeting is over,
the time is 19:00 of today.
This document will be returned,
then click on the return button
and I will select the individual
and the unit to participate.
For example, here I will invite the individual members.
I am creating for Phuong Cam Danh, right?
I'm gonna create my own github
I choose three students.
I choose a student who has a meeting
in the unit that must have a host.
For example, today the admin of the City Office
of the meeting must have the host as the director of the office
or the director of the number transfer office.
If you go to another meeting,
you don't have to choose the host,
you will hit the host down here.
For example, now the ward members
choose to go to another meeting,
you will hit the host down here.
And for this meeting document,
number 2373,
you want only the host to receive it Now
I will carry out a new meeting
And when you add new roles
that do not have the power to summon,
there will be no summon button here.
And if you have the power to summon,
there will be an additional summon button.
As you can see, there is a test meeting schedule
that I created this morning.
Now, I will add another schedule.
Learn about the number transfer project After that,
when you download the homepage,
there will be another session
on this number transfer project, right?
This session... In the morning,
it's the schedule for today,
and the upcoming schedule
is only for the upcoming meetings.
As for the schedule for this morning,
it will not be on this side anymore.
For those of you who go to other meetings,
I have just guided you, right?
You choose a meeting that is not managed,
and you select the meeting room of the Office of the Committee.
And you choose another participant.
And you will select the person in charge
here is the Office of the Office of the Ministry of Finance,
For example, I take the example like that, right?
Then you still enter the dates as usual here.
The time, the participants, etc.
of your unit as usual, right?
Invite individuals, invite units.
It's just that I don't choose the person in charge as my unit.
Because I don't go to class in my unit,
but I'm the leader, right?
There are two cases
that create such a schedule.
The next part is the file management module.
After that, there will be a guide to work with you
on the system
if you want to continue to operate.
Otherwise, there will be a Q&A section.
We will arrange a session for you to operate.
Or you can just record the videos
you operate and send them to the group.
We will help answer them.
All users will have a file list module.
For this file name menu,
the leader and the word of the unit
will have the right
to add a new one for the unit,
and the individual
will add the name of the individual.
You will go to the file list
and you will have to create a new application.
For example, this unit has not been named as an application yet.
In the morning,
I just filed for the board of directors.
Now, I change this user to a party member,
then this unit will not have an application name.
Then I will still create the application title as usual.
For example, a colleague of the Party,
Phuong, is an office specializing
in visiting documents, right?
Choose a file name
that does not have a name
that the document has not been When it's done,
I will create my own name for myself.
Because many people from the beginning
of the year
have created their own personal titles to save.
That is, it will also create the title of the application
according to the title of the application
that I have divided,
but the title of the application
for annual work
is not the beginning of the year
that has been registered immediately, right?
In the middle of the year,
it was registered and in the middle of May,
May, June, it was entered.
At the beginning of the year,
I actively created a set of documents
and I gave them to the staff.
to the beginning of the year,
then by the end of the year
I will put the amount of documents in it.
If you don't do it by the end of the year,
it will give you a full selection of documents,
it will be a lot and it will be long, right?
I will choose the density
and the storage time.
For example, this account is scheduled
to be stored for 10 years.
I will do the same again.
I have just completed the recording of the file title.
There is still no document or file inside.
Please click to see the details.
for you to collect the file into that file set.
For example, you will choose from the list,
you will be in the "All" tab.
You can choose this one at a time.
Or you can go to each tab.
You can also choose, for example,
this file is only the ones
that you scan from the machine,
then you will enter it here, right?
Enter the fields, the more you enter,
the more beautiful your file is.
I will do it again.
For the page that is uploaded from the paper,
you have to go to the page number.
You will have to count
the pages and type them in.
Because when you finish the application,
you must have the total number of pages.
Otherwise, the system will not let it end.
The system will automatically count
how many pages you have in this section.
There are three cases for the document menu.
The first case is that you are handed over
as the head of this document,
but you are also handed over as a partner,
then you can share with that person
For example, if I share the information with the office,
and I give the office the right to view it,
then in the file list of the office,
there will be a set of files
named "File 3M" but there will be no right
to add new files to it, but only to view.
If I give the right to edit,
it will be added new to it.
It's like a person is creating a document.
That's the first case.
The second case is if you are in charge of 3 files,
But if you quit your job, change your job
or go back to love,
you will hand over the job
to someone else, right? If you don't sign,
the other person won't have all the data of that document,
because they won't be able to receive the document,
the document,
or the document and the document.
I quit my job,
Then you will click on the end of the file
to transfer it to the history folder, right?
Yes, this is me trying to click on the end of the file
and the system has reported
that the end is over.
However, these two notes
are not lit because the system is automatically changing
the file name inside.
to automatically generate the samples
according to the regulations of the Central Library.
Here, the notification system
is uploading data
and saving these two files.
Later, after the compilation,
it will automatically generate two files,
one is the file list
and the other is the end result.
will have to wait from 1 to 3 minutes
for the system
to generate the data into the sample table.
And after you have finished formatting
the system here, the system will have this file
upload button.
The inside and outside of the file
will be visible
When you click the upload button,
it will automatically upload the file.
The system will create a form
to submit the application.
After submitting the application,
the system will automatically create a form
to submit the application.
That means the system will automatically do everything.
I will follow the steps of the process of saving documents and letters.
My work documents are in my diary.
This is the employment management menu,
the work documents,
the history of the history,
which Trung Quang is using for a few more days,
it will be deployed throughout the country.
History of writing,
according to the writing process.
In the case that the system
has completed all the data,
but you still need to edit this file,
it is still missing a lot of files inside,
you can open the lock to fix it here.
When you have downloaded it,
it will be locked like this.
The sample of the Central Committee
of the Department of Literacy
put in all the data in that case,
we were all forced to do it automatically.
We were all forced to do it
automatically inside the samples,
so it took a little longer to compile the data.
And if you look at the details of this application,
you can see all the details
of this application title.
It's like the white A4 paper
that you are pasting on the blue folder.
Every year, when you finish your documents,
you have to save them in a boxed blue folder, right?
And you paste the label on the outside.
What is the document?
From how many copies to how many?
And from which year, right?
The title of this document,
you do exactly the same.
And inside, you will put the paper in the blue folder like this,
then I will put the electronic version
in this electronic file.
I will move to another part,
I will be back in a moment. Please note
that there is one more case
that I want to note.
In the part of the received document to know,
when you receive the received document
to know, then you read the document,
then it is hidden inside,
but many people in the country report
that there is no more document here. Why?
Because when you open the search engine,
you will see that the status
is that the system
only captures the documents
that are not yet read, and the documents
that have been read It
will be hidden inside
and you will select the search status
and it will come out.
If you want to know more,
you can click on "Read" and click on "Find" button.
When the screen light is on,
it's very fast Today the internet is slow.
For example, if you go to your user,
there will be a lot of documents to know.
You just need to read one
and it will be hidden.
In the menu, you can see
that there are about 6 pictures.
Click on it. If you read the whole book,
it's only 85 pages. Hello.
This is page 54.
There are 2 pages for personal information.
You read one and it's 83, right?
Here, 85 is left because there are two individual versions.
When you click on it,
you will not see D83.
Now I want it to appear more.
I will select all the versions
that have been read. If you don't read it,
it will be a lot here. You see 88, right?
It's not lost,
but it will include the ones
that have been read, the dark black ones,
the ones that have not been read.
As far as I know,
usually your users will be .
83 when you open it to know, you say
I have 83 and this outside
is currently 85, it is not correct,
so that is for cases where you are literate,
there are two tables like this,
then you pay attention to me
and those who only have one role,
then it is only a personal document,
then it will not have a whole level,
it will only have a list to go down.
I'll show you a bit more sound.
I have just given you a brief overview
of the party's information system.
Khanh Hoa is the last one to be implemented.
I hope that Khanh Hoa
will be the last one to be implemented,
so our food and beverage team
will be more prioritized,
and we will have more support.
I hope you will have a good harvest today.
Now it's time to discuss and answer your questions.
Do you have any comments?
If you are sitting on the computer,
please take the steps so far.
If you have a document,
please create a test document
and transfer it to the staff in your unit
so that you have the data.
After that, I will perform the operation.
And I will help you to remove these test papers later.
Could you please enter the name
of the test version?
There is a tail behind is test
For the official calendar
and the leader calendar,
you can see that after you have chosen
to create a meeting,
you go to the official calendar
and you will see that the official calendar
will automatically be included.
As for the units that use the list,
you will have the function to view online lists here.
User manage meeting list
has the function to view online lists.
For example, when you go to the units,
you will often see the list outside the TV screen,
outside the list.
There is the word running.
As in the central,
all the corridors will be marked with this list of office leaders.
What is the leader's weekly calendar?
You will be able to see all the leaders' calendar.
I don't have... Bye.
You will see that the office manager
has a weekly schedule.
If you use this function,
you can click on the public section of the unit's structure.
If you have received a large amount,
you can ask about the next steps.
I will guide you later.
You can choose a week or a day here.
This is for your own convenience,
so that when you come to my office,
you will know that the leader
is having these meetings
that are not in the unit.
And some Hanoi units are tracking KPI
outside the calendar to let the units
know which units are on top
and which units are on the bottom,
so that the units can try harder to transfer the numbers.
Do you have any questions?
Please be strong.
If you have any questions about the parts
that you don't understand,
or any tasks that you need to be clear about,
or about the part that you think
you are not running correctly
with the unit you are running in reality.
However, if you want to change the course,
you have to take a short time.
I have trained a lot of units.
What are your opinions about this?
When we receive the document,
we submit the document.
After that, we submit the document
to the secretary of the leader.
Then the secretary of the leader
submits it to the leader.
Then the leader pays the secretary,
then the secretary pays back the document.
Then the document is transferred to the units.
If that's the paper process, right?
And if we do that with the electronic system,
it will slow down the document
and it will no longer transfer the number, right?
We have to submit from the document
to the leader
and then to the secretary at the same time.
And the secretary can visit the Miu.
and the leader can also transfer
and handle it right away.
After transferring, it will come to the unit
that is being implemented.
It is not that the leader
will transfer the document
to select the units
that the leader is directing.
Instead, the leader says
to hand over the teaching board to implement,
then select the teaching board
and transfer it.
Those are the shortterm steps.
Instead of having to take 6 steps
to get to the seminary, there are only 3
to 2 steps to get to the seminary.
There are still many steps
that you don't understand, you can ask.